1.8	NETWORK MODE MTP-F’24 editat el 12 de Desembre del 2024.
2.3	International Covenant Economic, Social and Cultural Rights (OHCHR, United Nations)
3.6	Article 1.
4.7	1. All peoples have the right of self-determination. By virtue of that right they freely determine their political status and freely pursue their economic, social and cultural development.	
5.2	https://www.ohchr.org/en/instruments-mechanisms/instruments/international-covenant-economic-social-and-cultural-rights	
